Guide to the Susan H. Douglas political Americana collection, [1783?]-1961.
Douglas, Susan H. Political Americana Collection, [1783?]-1961
- Series XV. Sheet Music
  - Lincoln Campaign Songster, 1959 (1864); 2214.SM0065 (Box 122)
- Series XVI. Scrapbooks & Scrapbook Items
  Scrapbooks: This series consists of 47 scrapbooks associated with particular election campaigns, one scrapbook on textiles, and individual items of particular note extracted from the scrapbooks. Mrs. Douglas included a combination of primary sources (particularly portraits but also a portion of a government document signed by Andrew Jackson) and secondary sources (especially newspaper and magazine clippings discussing electoral history) in her scrapbooks. Aside from extracted individual pieces, the scrapbooks will not be digitized by the Political Americana Project.
  - 1789-1792 Presidential Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0001 (Box 110)
  - Clippings from the October 28, 1789 Massachusetts Centennial, 2214.SY0001.43 (Box 81)
  - 1796-1804 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0002 (Box 110)
  - Tho. Jefferson. President of the United States of America, 1802; 2214.SY0002.23 (Box 81)
  - John Adams, 2214.SY0002.4a (Box 81)
  - 1808-1820 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0003 (Box 110)
  - James Madison, 2214.SY0003.12 (Box 81)
  - James Monroe, 2214.SY0003.31 (Box 81)
  - 1824 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0004 (Box 110)
  - J. Q. Adams, 1861; 2214.SY0004.13 (Box 83)
  - J.Q. Adams, 2214.SY0004.1e (Box 81)
  - 1828-1836 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0005 (Box 110)
  - Andrew Jackson, 2214.SY0005.10b (Box 81)
  - Andrew Jackson-Related Collodion Print Photographs, ca. 1897; 2214.SY0005.15 (Box 81)
  - M. Van Buren, 2214.SY0005.16b (Box 81)
  - Portion of United States Government Document with Seal, 1836; 2214.SY0005.30 (Box 83)
  - Andrew Jackson, 1861; 2214.SY0005.31 (Box 83)
  - M. Van Buren, 1862; 2214.SY0005.50 (Box 83)
  - Federal Land Sale Document with Seal, 1838; 2214.SY0005.53 (Box 94)
  - 1840 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0006 (Box 110)
  - W.H. Harrison, 1861; 2214.SY0006.15 (Box 83)
  - John Tyler, 1863; 2214.SY0006.42 (Box 83)
  - W. H. Harrison, 2214.SY0006.5c (Box 81)
  - John Tyler, 2214.SY0006.5d (Box 81)
  - 1844 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0007 (Box 111)
  - James K. Polk, 1862; 2214.SY0007.1 (Box 83)
  - James K. Polk, 2214.SY0007.11a (Box 81)
  - H. Clay, 1861; 2214.SY0007.13 (Box 83)
  - 1848 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0008 (Box 111)
  - Z Taylor, 2214.SY0008.18c (Box 81)
  - Zachary Taylor, 1863; 2214.SY0008.19 (Box 83)
  - M. Fillmore, 1862; 2214.SY0008.27 (Box 83)
  - Lewis Cass, 1862; 2214.SY0008.30 (Box 83)
  - 1852 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0009 (Box 111)
  - Winfield Scott, 1862; 2214.SY0009.16 (Box 83)
  - Franklin Pierce, 1864; 2214.SY0009.9 (Box 83)
  - 1856 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0010 (Box 111)
  - J.C. Fremont, 1862; 2214.SY0010.21 (Box 83)
  - James Buchanan, 1864; 2214.SY0010.9 (Box 83)
  - 1860 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 1: Republican, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0011 (Box 111)
  - Cabinet Officers, 1865; 2214.SY0011.32b (Box 81)
  - William H. Seward, 1863; 2214.SY0011.33 (Box 83)
  - 1860 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 2: Democratic, Constitutional Union, Confederacy, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0012 (Box 111)
  - S.A. Douglas, 1862; 2214.SY0012.10 (Box 83)
  - Edward Everett, 1863; 2214.SY0012.15 (Box 83)
  - Confederate States of America Treasury Department Seal, ca. 1861-1865; 2214.SY0012.21b (Box 81)
  - 1864 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 1: National Union/Republican, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0013 (Box 112)
  - Photograph of Lincoln Portrait Engraving, 2214.SY0013.11a (Box 81)
  - 1864 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 1: Johnson & Democratic, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0014 (Box 112)
  - Andrew Johnson, 2214.SY0014.2b (Box 81)
  - Geo. B. McClellan, 1862; 2214.SY0014.37 (Box 83)
  - Andrew Johnson, 1864; 2214.SY0014.6 (Box 83)
  - 1868 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0015 (Box 112)
  - Ulysses S. Grant-Related Photographic Post Cards, 2214.SY0015.27 (Box 81)
  - Hon. Horatio Seymour: Democratic Nominee for President, ca. 1868; 2214.SY0015.39a (Box 81)
  - Gen. Frank P. Blair: Democratic Nominee for Vice President, ca. 1868; 2214.SY0015.39b (Box 81)
  - U. S. Grant, 2214.SY0015.5e (Box 81)
  - U.S. Grant, 1863; 2214.SY0015.6 (Box 83)
  - 1872 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 1: Republican, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0016 (Box 112)
  - 1872 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 2: Liberal Republican / Democratic / Greeley, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0017 (Box 112)
  - 1872 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 3: Greeley, Labor Reform, Equal Rights, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0018 (Box 112)
  - 1876 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 1: Republican, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0019 (Box 113)
  - 1876 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 2: Democratic, Greenback, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0020 (Box 113)
  - 1880 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0021 (Box 113)
  - 1884 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0022 (Box 113)
  - Grover Cleveland, 2214.SY0022.14b (Box 81)
  - President Cleveland and Cabinet Members, ca. 1885-1887; 2214.SY0022.22a (Box 81)
  - T. A. Hendricks, 2214.SY0022.24b (Box 81)
  - 1888 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0023 (Box 113)
  - Mrs. Harrison's Bedroom, President's Mansion, Washington, D.C., ca. 1889-1892; 2214.SY0023.15c (Box 81)
  - 1892 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0024 (Box 113)
  - Cleveland Family Portrait, ca. 1893-1897; 2214.SY0024.15a (Box 81)
  - Mrs. Cleveland and Baby Ruth, 1893; 2214.SY0024.15b (Box 81)
  - Douglas Collection Exhibit Photograph, 1956, ca. 1956; 2214.SY0024.23d (Box 81)
  - 1896 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0025 (Box 113)
  - President McKinley visiting Major Gen' Wheeler, 1898; 2214.SY0025.18a (Box 81)
  - President McKinley at his desk in the White House, 1898; 2214.SY0025.19b (Box 81)
  - 1900 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0026 (Box 114)
  - President Roosevelt, 2214.SY0026.23 (Box 81)
  - 1904 Presidential Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0027 (Box 114)
  - 1908 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0028 (Box 114)
  - 1912 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0029 (Box 114)
  - 1916 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0030 (Box 114)
  - 1920 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0031 (Box 114)
  - 1924 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0032 (Box 115)
  - 1928 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0033 (Box 115)
  - 1932 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0034 (Box 115)
  - 1936 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0035 (Box 115)
  - 1940 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0036 (Box 115)
  - 1944 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0037 (Box 115)
  - 1948 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 1: Democratic, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0038 (Box 116)
  - 1948 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 2: Republican, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0039 (Box 116)
  - 1952 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 1: Republican, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0040 (Box 116)
  - 1952 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 2: Republican, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0041 (Box 116)
  - 1952 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 3: Democratic, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0042 (Box 116)
  - 1956 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 1: Republican, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0043 (Box 117)
  - 1956 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 2: Democratic, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0044 (Box 117)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 1: Democratic, Minors, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0045 (Box 117)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 2: Democratic, ca. 1961; 2214.SY0046 (Box 117)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign Scrapbook, Vol. 3: Republican, ca. 1960; 2214.SY0047 (Box 117)
  - Kerchiefs Scrapbook, ca. 1938-ca. 1960; 2214.SY0048 (Box TBD)
- Series XVII. Trinkets
  Trinkets: This series contains a variety of medals, medallions, pins, pendants, and other jewelry forms, including ferrotype portrait pins. Almost all of the items in this series have been cataloged as groups rather than at the item level. Mrs. Douglas artfully arranged these item groupings, frequently incorporating materials from other categories for visual effect.
  - Washington Inauguration Items, ca. 1789-1877; 2214.TK0000 (Box 171)
  - Jackson Campaign and Memorial Items, ca. 1828-1845; 2214.TK0001 (Box 171)
  - Jackson-Van Buren Promotional and Satirical Items, ca. 1832-1837; 2214.TK0001a (Box 204)
  - Anti-Van Buren and Pro-Webster Medals, ca. 1837-1841; 2214.TK0001b (Box 171)
  - Van Buren Campaign and Commemorative Items, ca. 1840-1900; 2214.TK0002 (Box 177)
  - William Henry Harrison Campaign and Memorial Items, ca. 1840-1841; 2214.TK0003 (Box 177)
  - Tyler Commemorative Items, 2214.TK0003a (Box 203)
  - William Henry Harrison Campaign Buttons, ca. 1840; 2214.TK0005 (Box 203)
  - Whig and Henry Clay Items, ca. 1834-1848; 2214.TK0006 (Box 225)
  - Henry Clay-Frelinghuysen Campaign Items, ca. 1844; 2214.TK0007 (Box 203)
  - Henry Clay Commemorative Items, ca. 1852; 2214.TK0008 (Box 171)
  - Polk-Dallas Campaign Items, ca. 1844; 2214.TK0009 (Box 172)
  - Taylor-Fillmore Items, ca. 1846-1960; 2214.TK0010 (Box 225)
  - Taylor Portrait Medal and Clipping, ca. 1847-1848; 2214.TK0010a (Box 178)
  - Fillmore Commemorative Items, 2214.TK0010b (Box 203)
  - Cass Campaign Items, ca. 1848; 2214.TK0011 (Box 203)
  - Pierce-King Campaign and Commemorative Items, ca. 1852-1960; 2214.TK0012 (Box 172)
  - Winfield Scott Campaign and Commemorative Items, ca. 1852-1861; 2214.TK0013 (Box 178)
  - Buchanan-Breckinridge Campaign and Commemorative Items, ca. 1856-1960; 2214.TK0014 (Box 172)
  - Frémont Campaign and Commemorative Items, ca. 1856-1929; 2214.TK0015 (Box 179)
  - Lincoln-Hamlin Campaign Items, ca. 1860-1861; 2214.TK0016 (Box 179)
  - Douglas Campaign and Memorial Items, ca. 1860-1866; 2214.TK0018 (Box 180)
  - Douglas-Herschel V. Johnson Ferrotype Pendants, ca. 1860; 2214.TK0019 (Box 204)
  - Breckinridge-Lane Campaign Items, ca. 1860; 2214.TK0020 (Box 204)
  - Bell-Everett Ferrotype Pendants, ca. 1860; 2214.TK0021 (Box 203)
  - Bell-Everett Campaign Items, ca. 1860; 2214.TK0022 (Box 172)
  - Confederate States of America Items, ca. 1861-1862; 2214.TK0023 (Box 180)
  - U.S. Presidential Portrait and Residence Medals Series, ca. 1861-1865; 2214.TK0023a (Box 181)
  - Lincoln-Andrew Johnson Campaign and Commemorative Items, ca. 1864-1865; 2214.TK0024 (Box 181)
  - Lincoln-Andrew Johnson Campaign Items, ca. 1864; 2214.TK0025 (Box 204)
  - McClellan Military and Campaign Items, ca. 1861-1878; 2214.TK0026 (Box 182)
  - McClellan-Pendleton Campaign Items, ca. 1863-1864; 2214.TK0027 (Box 205)
  - Frémont-Cochrane Campaign Items, ca. 1864; 2214.TK0028 (Box 205)
  - Lincoln Memorial Items, ca. 1865-1920; 2214.TK0029 (Box 182)
  - Andrew Johnson and George Washington Items, ca. 1860-1960; 2214.TK0030 (Box 173)
  - Lincoln Commemorative Medallions, ca. 1865-1909; 2214.TK0031 (Box 173)
  - Grant-Colfax Campaign Items, ca. 1868; 2214.TK0032 (Box 183)
  - Grant Campaign and Memorial Items, ca. 1868-1885; 2214.TK0033 (Box 183)
  - Grant-Colfax Campaign and Commemorative Items, ca. 1868-1960; 2214.TK0033a (Box 184)
  - Display Card with Seymour Ferrotype Portrait Pins, ca. 1868; 2214.TK0034 (Box 184)
  - Seymour-Blair Campaign Items, ca. 1868; 2214.TK0035 (Box 185)
  - Seymour-Blair Campaign Items, ca. 1868; 2214.TK0035a (Box 185)
  - Grant-Colfax and Grant-Henry Wilson Campaign Items, ca. 1868-1872; 2214.TK0036 (Box 206)
  - Grant and Henry Wilson Items, ca. 1872-1885; 2214.TK0037 (Box 186)
  - Greeley Campaign and Memorial Items, ca. 1872; 2214.TK0038 (Box 173)
  - Greeley, Brown, and Thurman Campaign Items, ca. 1872-1888; 2214.TK0039 (Box 186)
  - "Centennial Candidates for 1876" Portrait Pins, 2214.TK0040 (Box 205)
  - Hayes-Wheeler Campaign Items, ca. 1876; 2214.TK0041 (Box 206)
  - Hayes-Wheeler Items, ca. 1876-1960; 2214.TK0042 (Box 187)
  - Tilden-Hendricks Photographic Campaign Pins, ca. 1876; 2214.TK0043 (Box 226)
  - Tilden-Hendricks Promotional and Satirical Items, ca. 1876-1880; 2214.TK0044 (Box 206)
  - Garfield Campaign and Memorial Items, ca. 1880-1960; 2214.TK0045 (Box 187)
  - Garfield-Arthur Campaign Items, ca. 1880; 2214.TK0046 (Box 205)
  - Arthur Inauguration Commemorative Items, ca. 1881; 2214.TK0047 (Box 173)
  - Hancock-English Promotional and Satirical Items, ca. 1880; 2214.TK0048 (Box 206)
  - Hancock-English Campaign Items, ca. 1880; 2214.TK0049 (Box 188)
  - Cleveland-Hendricks Campaign and Inaugural Items, ca. 1884-1885; 2214.TK0050 (Box 188)
  - Cleveland-Hendricks Campaign Items, ca. 1884; 2214.TK0051 (Box 189)
  - Grover-Frances Folsom Cleveland Marriage Commemorative Items, ca. 1886-1888; 2214.TK0051a (Box 189)
  - Blaine-Logan Campaign Items, ca. 1884; 2214.TK0052 (Box 190)
  - Blaine-Logan Campaign Items, ca. 1884; 2214.TK0053 (Box 190)
  - Cleveland-Thurman Campaign Items, ca. 1888; 2214.TK0054 (Box 191)
  - Cleveland-Thurman Campaign Items, ca. 1888; 2214.TK0055 (Box 191)
  - Cleveland-Thurman Campaign Items, ca. 1888; 2214.TK0056 (Box 192)
  - Benjamin Harrison Campaign Items, ca. 1888-1892; 2214.TK0057 (Box 192)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton Campaign and Inaugural Items, ca. 1888-1889; 2214.TK0058 (Box 193)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton Campaign Items, ca. 1888; 2214.TK0059 (Box 193)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson Campaign items, ca. 1892-1893; 2214.TK0060 (Box 194)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson Campaign Items, ca. 1892; 2214.TK0061 (Box 208)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson Inaugural Items, ca. 1893; 2214.TK0062 (Box 208)
  - Benjamin Harrison Campaign Items, ca. 1888-1892; 2214.TK0063 (Box 194)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Reid Campaign Items, ca. 1892; 2214.TK0064 (Box 195)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Reid Lapel Studs, ca. 1840-1892; 2214.TK0065 (Box 207)
  - McKinley Items, ca. 1892-1901; 2214.TK0066 (Box 195)
  - McKinley-Hobart Campaign Items, ca. 1896; 2214.TK0067 (Box 196)
  - McKinley "The 'Hurrah' Campaign Procession Badge, ca. 1896; 2214.TK0069 (Box 209)
  - "Bryan Money," 1896-1900, 2214.TK0070 (Box 209)
  - "Bryan Money,", ca. 1896; 2214.TK0071 (Box 210)
  - "Bryan Money,", ca. 1896; 2214.TK0072 (Box 210)
  - Bryan Campaign Items, ca. 1896-1908; 2214.TK0073 (Box 174)
  - Bryan-Sewall Campaign Items, ca. 1896; 2214.TK0074 (Box 174)
  - McKinley-Theodore Roosevelt Campaign and Inaugural Items, ca. 1900-1901; 2214.TK0075 (Box 196)
  - McKinley-Theodore Roosevelt Campaign items, ca. 1900; 2214.TK0076 (Box 197)
  - Bryan-Stevenson Campaign Items, ca. 1900; 2214.TK0077 (Box 207)
  - McKinley Memorial Items, ca. 1901; 2214.TK0078 (Box 211)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Presidential Items, ca. 1901-1909; 2214.TK0079 (Box 174)
  - Theodore Roosevelt-Fairbanks Campaign and Inaugural Items, ca. 1904-1905; 2214.TK0080 (Box 211)
  - Theodore Roosevelt-Fairbanks Campaign Items, ca. 1904; 2214.TK0081 (Box 197)
  - Parker-Davis Campaign Items, ca. 1904; 2214.TK0082 (Box 174)
  - Parker-Davis Campaign Items, ca. 1904; 2214.TK0083 (Box 205)
  - Taft-Sherman Items, ca. 1908-1909; 2214.TK0084 (Box 212)
  - Taft-Sherman Campaign Items, ca. 1908; 2214.TK0085 (Box 198)
  - Bryan-Kern Campaign Items, ca. 1908; 2214.TK0086 (Box 212)
  - Wilson-Marshall Campaign and Inaugural Items, ca. 1912-1917; 2214.TK0087 (Box 213)
  - Woodrow Wilson Satirical and Commemorative Medals, ca. 1914-1919; 2214.TK0088 (Box 224)
  - Progressive Party Membership Certificate, 1912; 2214.TK0088a (Box 175)
  - Theodore Roosevelt-related Items, ca. 1910-1912; 2214.TK0089 (Box 198)
  - Hughes Campaign Items, ca. 1906-1916; 2214.TK0090 (Box 225)
  - Taft-Sherman Campaign Items, ca. 1908-1912; 2214.TK0091 (Box 213)
  - Harding Campaign, Inauguration, and Memorial Items, ca. 1920-1923; 2214.TK0092 (Box 175)
  - Coolidge Inaugural Medallion, ca. 1923; 2214.TK0092a (Box 207)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.TK0094 (Box -)
  - Cox-Franklin D. Roosevelt Campaign Items, ca. 1920; 2214.TK0095 (Box 205)
  - Coolidge-Dawes Campaign Items, ca. 1924; 2214.TK0096 (Box 176)
  - Hoover-Curtis Campaign and Inaugural Items, ca. 1928-1932; 2214.TK0097 (Box 214)
  - Hoover-Curtis Campaign Items, ca. 1928-1932; 2214.TK0098 (Box 214)
  - Smith-Robinson Campaign Items, ca. 1928; 2214.TK0099 (Box 175)
  - Smith-Robinson Campaign Items, ca. 1928; 2214.TK0100 (Box 225)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt-Garner Campaign and Inaugural Items, ca. 1932-1936; 2214.TK0101 (Box 215)
  - Willkie-McNary Campaign Items, ca. 1940; 2214.TK0102 (Box 175)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Campaign and Inaugural Items, ca. 1933-1945; 2214.TK0103 (Box 176)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Inauguration and Commemorative Items, ca. 1945-1960; 2214.TK0104 (Box 176)
  - Dewey Campaign Items, ca. 1944-1948; 2214.TK0105 (Box 199)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Campaign Items, ca. 1932-1944; 2214.TK0106 (Box 200)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt and Truman Campaign and Presidential Items, ca. 1944-1949; 2214.TK0106a (Box 215)
  - Matchbook from Trinket Box 2214.TK0106, ca. 1932-1944; 2214.TK0106b (Box 227)
  - Landon-Knox Campaign Items, ca. 1936; 2214.TK0107 (Box 200)
  - Landon-Knox and Philander Knox Campaign Items, ca. 1908-1936; 2214.TK0108 (Box 201)
  - Willkie Campaign Items, ca. 1940; 2214.TK0109 (Box 216)
  - Willkie Campaign Items, ca. 1940; 2214.TK0110 (Box 216)
  - Willkie Campaign Items, ca. 1940; 2214.TK0110a (Box 217)
  - Matchbooks from Trinket Box 2214.TK0110, ca. 1940; 2214.TK0110b (Box 227)
  - Truman and Democratic Donkey Items, ca. 1948; 2214.TK0111 (Box 176)
  - Dewey-Warren Campaign Items, ca. 1948; 2214.TK0112 (Box 176)
  - Dewey-Warren Campaign Items, ca. 1948; 2214.TK0113 (Box 199)
  - Matchbooks from Trinket Box 2214.TK0113, ca. 1948; 2214.TK0113a (Box 227)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Campaign Jewelry, ca. 1952; 2214.TK0114 (Box 217)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Campaign Jewelry, ca. 1952; 2214.TK0115 (Box 201)
  - Eisenhower Campaign Items, ca. 1952; 2214.TK0116 (Box 218)
  - Stevenson Campaign Items, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.TK0117 (Box 218)
  - Stevenson Campaign Items, ca. 1952; 2214.TK0117a (Box 225)
  - Eisenhower Campaign and Commemorative Items, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.TK0118 (Box 225)
  - Eisenhower Campaign Items, ca. 1956; 2214.TK0118a (Box 202)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Campaign Items, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.TK0118b (Box 202)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Commemorative Items, ca. 1933-1938; 2214.TK0119 (Box 224)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt and Truman Items, ca. 1945-1946; 2214.TK0120 (Box 222)
  - Presidential Commemorative Medal Series, ca. 1945; 2214.TK0121 (Box 225)
  - Harriman Donkey Pin, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.TK0122 (Box 207)
  - Nixon-Lodge Campaign Bracelets and Pendant, ca. 1960; 2214.TK0123 (Box 221)
  - Nixon Republican Elephant Pins, ca. 1960; 2214.TK0124 (Box 221)
  - Nixon Campaign Items, ca. 1960; 2214.TK0125 (Box 221)
  - Nixon Cuff Links, ca. 1960; 2214.TK0126 (Box 226)
  - Nixon "Put The Right Man in the Right Spot" Puzzle, ca. 1960; 2214.TK0127 (Box 226)
  - Kennedy-Lyndon B. Johnson Campaign Items, ca. 1960; 2214.TK0128 (Box 221)
  - Republican Elephant Campaign Cookie Cutter, ca. 1960; 2214.TK0129 (Box 226)
  - Nixon-Lodge Campaign Items, ca. 1960; 2214.TK0130 (Box 226)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign Matchbooks, ca. 1960; 2214.TK0130a (Box 227)
  - Eisenhower "Ike" / Elephant Badge, ca. 1952-1956; 2214.TK0131 (Box 226)
  - Eisenhower Earrings & Necklaces, ca. 1956; 2214.TK0132 (Box 226)
  - Theodore Roosevelt-Fairbanks "1904 Washington" Badge, 2214.TK0133 (Box 226)
- Series XVIII. Textiles
  Textiles: This series contains a variety of politically-related textile forms, including bandanas, handkerchiefs, and yardage.
  - William Henry Harrison Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1840; 2214.TX0001 (Map-case EE-11)
  - Greeley Campaign Textile, ca. 1872; 2214.TX0002 (Box 108)
  - Zachary Taylor Portrait Textile, ca. 1848; 2214.TX0003 (Box 154)
  - Zachary Taylor Portrait Textile, ca.1848; 2214.TX0004 (Box 154)
  - Washington Portrait Textile, 2214.TX0005 (Box 109)
  - Andrew Jackson Portrait Textile, ca. 1829; 2214.TX0006 (Box 154)
  - Cleveland-Thurman "Our Candidates 1888" Portrait Handkerchief, 2214.TX0007 (Box 108)
  - Washington-Benjamin Harrison Portrait Textile, ca. 1889; 2214.TX0008 (Map-case -)
  - Harrison-Morton "Our Choice 1888" Portrait Handkerchief, 2214.TX0009 (Box 109)
  - Grand National Republican Banner Textile, 1880; 2214.TX0010 (Box 108)
  - Theodore Roosevelt-Fairbanks "Protection to American Industries" Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1904; 2214.TX0011 (Box TBD)
  - Lincoln & Johnson / Fenton & Alvord Textile, ca. 1864; 2214.TX0012 (Box 109)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton "Our Choice 1888" Portrait Handkerchief, 2214.TX0013 (Box 104)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1932; 2214.TX0014 (Box 104)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton "Tippecanoe and Morton Too" Handkerchief, ca. 1888; 2214.TX0015 (Box 109)
  - Theodore Roosevelt "TR" Portrait Handkerchief, 1912; 2214.TX0016 (Box 109)
  - Cleveland-Thurman "Public Office A Public Trust" Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1888; 2214.TX0017 (Box 108)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton "Protection" Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1888; 2214.TX0018 (Box 108)
  - Garfield-Arthur Portrait Textile, ca. 1880; 2214.TX0019 (Box 109)
  - Hoover "Our President" Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1932; 2214.TX0020 (Box 104)
  - McKinley-Hobart "Sound Money" Portrait Textile, ca. 1896; 2214.TX0021 (Box 104)
  - Blaine-Logan Portrait Handkerchief, 1884; 2214.TX0022 (Box 109)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson "Tariff Reform" Portrait Handkerchief, 1892; 2214.TX0023 (Box 109)
  - Hancock-English "Liberty" Portrait Handkerchief, 1880; 2214.TX0024 (Box 104)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton "Protection Home Industries" Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1888; 2214.TX0025 (Box 109)
  - McKinley-Hobart "Protection Republican Prosperity" Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1896; 2214.TX0026 (Box 109)
  - Willkie "God Bless America" Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1940; 2214.TX0027 (Box 107)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt "United States Always" Portrait Textile, ca. 1940; 2214.TX0028 (Box 104)
  - Cleveland & Thurman 1888 Campaign Bandanna, 2214.TX0029 (Box 104)
  - Theodore Roosevelt "Progressive Battle Flag" Portrait Textile, 1912; 2214.TX0030 (Box 108)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton "Protect Home Industry" Portrait Handkerchief, 1888; 2214.TX0031 (Box 108)
  - U.S. Grant, Lt. General Portrait Textile, ca. 1868; 2214.TX0032 (Box 108)
  - Blaine-Logan Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1884; 2214.TX0033 (Box 104)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton "The Old Flag and Protection" Portrait Handkerchief, 1888; 2214.TX0034 (Box 109)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton American Flag Handkerchief, 1888; 2214.TX0034A (Box 109)
  - McKinley "Our Choice for President" Portrait Textile, 1896; 2214.TX0035 (Map-case -)
  - George Washington at the Altar of Liberty, ca. 1783; 2214.TX0036 (Map-case -)
  - American Independence 1776 Textile, ca. 1783; 2214.TX0037 (Box TBD)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Reid "Protection / Reciprocity" Portrait Handkerchief, 1892; 2214.TX0038 (Box 105)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Reid "Protection And Reciprocity" Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1892; 2214.TX0039 (Box 105)
  - William Henry Harrison "Commander in Chief of the Northwestern Army" Portrait Textile, ca. 1840; 2214.TX0040 (Map-case -)
  - Gloire Aux Américains: Souvenir de France, ca. 1915-1920; 2214.TX0041 (Box 107)
  - "Re-Elect Roosevelt" Handkerchief, ca. 1940; 2214.TX0042 (Box 107)
  - "Win with Ike for President" Portrait Handkerchief, ca. 1952; 2214.TX0043 (Map-case -)
  - William Henry Harrison Campaign Textile, ca. 1840; 2214.TX0044 (Box 107)
  - William Henry Harrison "Harrison and Reform" Portrait Textile, ca. 1840; 2214.TX0045 (Box 107)
  - Washington "The Love of Truth Mark the Boy" Textile, ca. 1806; 2214.TX0046 (Box 107)